1. I'm taking the IELTS test because I want to study overseas.
2. There's a population of 21 million in Beijing, so it's jam-packed wherever you go.
3. I was born and raised in a small town in the south of China, and I have two loving and caring parents.
4. Some of my friends are aiming to go and study in Australia, whereas my goal is to go to the UK.
5. The Mid-Autumn Festival falls on the 15th day of the 8th month of the lunar calendar.
6. It's usually scorching hot in my hometown in the summertime. The temperature can even be 40 degrees Celsius sometimes.
7. I was amazed at all the vivid colours while I was snorkelling and looking down at the underwater world.
8. It's highly likely that we will use the computer more and more and the pen less and less in the future.
9. I don't suppose shared bicycles are the best way to reduce traffic congestion.
10. The government is investing heavily in electric buses, and I'm totally on their side.
11. I wish I could speak English better. That way, I would be able to travel the world without any difficulty.
12. I have a penchant for cooking, and I seldom eat out because I'm only satisfied with the food I cook.
13. My grandad is already in his late 70s, but he is still as fit as a fiddle because he eats well and takes exercise every day.
14. Many people from the countryside and small towns flock to large cities in search of a better job and a better future.
15. Although some areas are unaffected by climate change now, it's a pressing problem that has to be dealt with immediately.
16. Celebrities are constantly followed by paparazzi and worried about being recognised on the street when they are on vacation and just want to relax.
17. I'm an Aquarius, and it's said that people like me are born thinkers.
18. One of my cousins is crazy about travelling, and she has been to dozens of countries over the past 10 years.
19. If this park were closer to my apartment, I guess I would go there more often.
20. Fairweather friends are definitely the kind of friends we don't want.
21. Smartphones have blurred the lines between work and home lives, and we often communicate with our colleagues and bosses after work now.
22. It's OK if teenagers play video games in moderation. All work and no play makes Jack a dull boy.
23. It's obvious that being multilingual gives people an advantage in the workplace.
24. Word of mouth advertising is the most effective form of advertising.
25. Looking at old photos brings back memories.
26. I went to the biggest theatre in town for a fascinating play last weekend.
27. The bus is the cheapest way to get around, even though it's overcrowded most of the time.
28. Success comes in various forms. It could be having a high social status, earning a seven figure salary, or simply feeling happy every day.
29. It's best to get away from it all and go on an excursion on the weekend.
30. Spending money on experiences, especially with other people, is what makes us truly happy.